Guide to the Harrison Lee papers, 1928-1992 MS2011
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Harrison Lee papers
1928-1992
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Lee, Harrison
MS2011
9.5 Linear Feet
Collection consists of the D.C. Comprehensive Plan including documents relating to the comprehensive plan for the National Capital; manuscript and committee records; printed ephemera; newspaper articles; newsletters; magazine articles; brochures and guidebooks; awards and certificates. The material dates from 1928-92.
Restrictions on Access
Some records may be restricted.
Acquisition Information
In June of 1996, Anna L. Lee donated the papers of her late husband Harrison Lee to the George Washington University (GWU) Gelman Library. All rights and interests were transferred to the Department of Special Collections.
Historical or Biographical Note
Harrison Lee (1920-1993) worked for the U.S. Army and the CIA as an intelligence analyst. After his retirement in 1973, Lee became an active leader in the Washington, D.C. Chinatown community. The collection material reflects Lee's involvement as a community activist and leader in Washington's Chinatown for more than 20 years. The period covered in this collection coincided with one of the most interesting and active phases of redevelopment and urban planning in the city.
Collection Scope and Content
This collection consists of the D.C. Comprehensive Plan including documents relating to the comprehensive plan for the National Capital; manuscript and committee records; printed ephemera; newspaper articles; newsletters; magazine articles; brochures and guidebooks; awards and certificates. The material dates from 1928-92.
Collection Organization
Organized into seven series: D.C. urban planning/ D.C. comprehensive plan, Community and business organizations, Wah Luck House, Miscellaneous/ peripheral projects and concerns of the Chinese Community in Washington, Printed ephemera, Awards and certificates, and Blueprints.
City planning; Business; Housing; Chinatown (Washington, D.C.); Washington (D.C.); Wah Luck House (Washington, D.C.)
- D.C. urban planning/D.C. comprehensive plan, 1977-1988; MS2011 Series 1; 2 Linear feet
  Scope and Contents note
  This series consists of the DC Urban Planning/DC Comprehensive plan. The D.C. Comprehensive Plan was adopted by the D.C. City Council and enacted into law in 1984 after years of full community review and comment. Until the Home Rule Act of 1974, the federal National Capital Planning Commission was the agency responsible for planning for the district. The Home Rule Act gave local planning authority to the city while N.C.P.C. retained an "overlay" authority for the federal functions. The D.C. Comprehensive Plan plotted a 20-year course for the development of the city. The series consists of general information, DC Downtown Development and Chinatown Development. The material dates from 1977-88.
  - DC Municipal Planning Office publication, "Comprehensive Planning Process", 10 pages, 1977 January (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Comprehensive Plan for the National Capital: District of Columbia Components, staff Draft, 1982 September (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Urban Design Elements -- Chapter 7 of Comprehensive Plan, Staff Draft, 1983 May (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Proposed Presentation and Historic Features Elements, Chapter 8 of Comprehensive Plan, 1983 May 17 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Downtown DC -- Chapter 9 of the Comprehensive Plan, 1982 July (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Implementation Report, Chapter 10 of comprehensive plan, 1983 August (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Additional Information for Comprehensive Plan, 1983 August 18 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Community Comments Downtown, 1983 August (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Community Participation in the Planning Process, 1983 August (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Planning Report, 1983 August (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence -- Organization of Chinese Americans supporting the Comprehensive plan, 1983 November 04 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Public hearing on Bill 5-282 of Comprehensive Plan, witness list, testimony, newspaper article, 1983 November 14 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Objectives and Policies Relating to Chinatown, 1984 January 31 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Land Use Element, 1984 August (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Progress Report on the Comprehensive Plan -- Review of Resolution of 1986, 1986 May 20 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - DC Office of Planning -- Implementing the District Elements of the Comprehensive Plan for the National Capital, 2nd edition, 1988 April (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - 7-402 "A Proposed Resolution" to the Comprehensive plan, 1988 May 12 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Transcripts of June 21, 1988 public hearing on PR 7-402, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Committee Report on PR 7-402, 1988 July 12 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Bill 7-524 -- amendment of 1984 Land Use Amendment Act of 1984, 1988 September 23 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Four Land Use Maps (generalized, residential, commercial and production, public and institutional) and accompanying guide, 1985 September (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - DC Office of Planning -- Implementing the District Elements of the Comprehensive Plan for the National Capital, 3rd edition, 1990 April (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - DC Downtown Development: Reaction of the Committee of the Whole to the proposed development of the 12th and G St Area, correspondence, August-September, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - DC Downtown Development: Procurement of funds for development on 6th and H St, correspondence and Washington Post article, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - DC Downtown Development: DC national Capital Downtown Committee, Inc. -- Highlights in Downtown Washington, Downtown progress Brochure, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - DC Downtown Development: Correspondence -- President Carter's approval of the Downtown Progress, 1977 February 11 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - DC Downtown Development: Annual reports on the progress of the Downtown progress, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - DC Downtown Development: Downtown Development Task Force Draft Operating Principles, 1978 November 15 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - DC Downtown Development: Downtown press releases, 1977-1979 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - DC Downtown Development: DC Office of Planning and Development -- "Land Use Assessment: downtown Washington DC" -- Discussion Draft, 1981 October (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - DC Downtown Development: Downtown: A People Place -- Greater Washington Board of Trade, original report (October 20 1980) DC government's response (March 1981), 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - DC Downtown Development: A Living Downtown: Planning Concepts, 1981 April (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - DC Downtown Development: DC Downtown "Working Paper #2 -- The Base case", 1981 November 30 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - DC Downtown Development: DC Office of Planning and Development "living Downtown" working paper, 1982 January (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - DC Downtown Development: Mayor's Downtown Committee -- Map, 1982 July (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - DC Downtown Development: A Summary of: A Living Downtown, 1984 April (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - DC Downtown Development: DC Preservation of Historic Buildings In the Pennsylvania Avenue Historic Site, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - DC Downtown Development: DC Mayor's Commission on Downtown Housing -- "Downtown Housing in Washington DC: realizing the Goal of a Living Downtown", 1988 November (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - DC Downtown Development: Downtown Streetscape -- Draft report, undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - DC Downtown Development: Draft Statement of Urban Design Goals and Objectives, undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - DC Downtown Development: Committee's Membership Lists, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - DC Downtown Development: Various Committee mailing Lists, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - DC Downtown Development: Issues Concerning the retail core, 1980 January (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - DC Downtown Development: Downtown Planning Issues, 1981 December 17 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - DC Downtown Development: Necessity for an interim committee to regulate development before finalization of Downtown Plan, 1981 December 19 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - DC Downtown Development: Maps -- General Concepts and Chinatown, 1981 September (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - DC Downtown Development: Summation of Preliminary Findings of the Urban Design Subcommittee, 1981 December 09 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - DC Downtown Development: Downtown Study for Washington DC -- Various Drafts, 1981 December 31-1982 March 11 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - DC Downtown Development: Downtown Urban Design Plan -- Adopted Goals and Recommendations, after 1981, undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - DC Downtown Development: Second Downtown Work session -- Major Policy Issues, 1982 February 04 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - DC Downtown Development: Downtown Design Review and Supporting Documentation, 1982 February 23 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - DC Downtown Development: Priorities for Downtown, 1982 March 09 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - DC Downtown Development: Downtown Issues unresolved by the Downtown Sketch Plan, 1982 April 13 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - DC Downtown Development: Outstanding Issues, 1982 April 06 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - DC Downtown Development: Downtown Development District -- Draft, 1989 February 22 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - DC Downtown Development: Recommended Urban Design Policies and Actions, undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - DC Downtown Development: DC Office of Planning and Development -- Downtown Zoning Concepts -- Draft, 1982 February 12 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - DC Downtown Development: Key Features of Chinatown Zoning Provisions, undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - DC Downtown Development: Downtown Development District -- Zoning issues, Chinatown Examples, undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - DC Downtown Development: Downtown Development Zone -- First Discussion draft, 1988 July 25 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - DC Downtown Development: Testimony by downtown partnership on Zoning Case #88-7, 1988 September 08 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - DC Downtown Development: Downtown Development District -- Summary of Changes in Base Zones, 1989 February 22 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - DC Downtown Development: DC Zoning Panel Confirms Retail Rules, The Washington Post, 1989 March 18 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - DC Downtown Development: Changes made to zoning of the housing provisions, November August, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - DC Downtown Development: Correspondence -- view against down zoning, 1989 November 15 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - DC Downtown Development: Critique of the Downtown District Proposal to the DC Zoning Commission, 1989 December 06 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - DC Downtown Development: DC Zoning Commission Case #89-25 -- Downtown Development District Housing/Mixed Use Examples of Office Planning, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - DC Downtown Development: DC Zoning Commission -- Notice of Public Hearing Case #89-25, 1990 February 22 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - DC Downtown Development: Presentation of the Downtown Partnership to the Zoning Committee on Case #89-25, 1990 February 26 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - DC Downtown Development: DC Office of Planning -- "Rezoning for a Living Downtown", 1990 February (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - DC Downtown Development: DC Zoning Commission Case #89-25 Downtown Development District Witness List, 1990 March 01 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - DC Downtown Development: DC Zoning Commission Case #89-25 Downtown Development District -- Community testimony by Bosco Lee, 1990 March 01 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - DC Downtown Development: Notes on the hearing testimony and information, 1990 March 02 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - DC Downtown Development: Projected adverse effects of zoning restrictions on Chinatown, undated (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - DC Downtown Development: US National Capital Planning Commission, "Downtown Design and Development" 1974 (also cataloged in SPEC HT168.W3.05 1974) (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - DC Downtown Development: DC Downtown Progress -- "Downtown Washington: A Walking Guide", 1976 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - DC Downtown Development: Public/Private partnership in Downtown Revitalization, promotional publication, 1976 October (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - DC Downtown Development: "Streets for people" -- brochure and correspondence, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - DC Downtown Development: DC Office of Business and Economic Development "DC More than the Nations Capital" promotional materials, 1980 December (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - DC Downtown Development: DC Office of Planning and Development "Sign Regulations in the District of Columbia", 1981 March (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - DC Downtown Development: Metropolitan Washington Planning and Housing Association "Housing: New Ways to Wage the War" Annual Report, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - DC Downtown Development: "Downtown Afoot: Paving the Way for Pedestrians" -- GWU Department of Urban and Regional Planning (also in SPEC NA2543.P4.DL8 1981), 1981 July (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - DC Downtown Development: DC Department of Public Works, "Downtown Street Network Study", 1985 November 01 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - DC Downtown Development: DC Department of Public Works, "Downtown Street Network Study Project", 1986 February 19 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - DC Downtown Development: "Affordable Housing?" article in the Real Estate Reporter, 1990 October (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - DC Downtown Development: DC Downtown Loop Bus Plan, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Chinatown Development: Chinese Community Planning, Contract No DC-RLA-1727, Memorandum No 1 & 2, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Chinatown Development: Correspondence Making Chinatown visible, 1977 December (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Chinatown Development: Installation of "Chinatown" Directional Signs, August and September, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Chinatown Development: A Living Downtown for Washington DC -- Chinatown, various drafts, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Chinatown Development: Recommendations for the Downtown Plan -- Chinatown, 1982 July (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Chinatown Development: Strategies for the Economic Development of Chinatown, 1982 September 15 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Chinatown Development: List of architect candidates, 1984 May 04 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Chinatown Development: Prospective architect's resume and sketches, 1984 June 25 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Chinatown Development: Preliminary Concept Development of Chinatown park on 6th and I St, 1988 July (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Chinatown Development: Chinatown Design Standards, AEPA, 1988 August 14 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Chinatown Development: Chinatown -- Chinese Design Elements, 1988 November 20 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Chinatown Development: DC Chinatown Emergency Action Steps, 1988 November 20 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Chinatown Development: AEPA (Architects Engineer Planner Association "The Future of Washington's Chinatown: Extinction or Distinction", undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Chinatown Development: Office of Planning -- Chinatown Design Review Procedures, 1991 February 01 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Chinatown Development: Architectural design for the METRO site at 7th St, undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Community and business organizations, 1988-1992; MS2011 Series 2; 2 Linear feet
  This series consists of materials related to the Chinatown Steering Committee, Chinese Consolidated Benevolent Association of Washington, D.C., Washington Chinatown Development Company Incorporated, Chinatown Economic Development Company, D.C. Downtown Partnership, and the D.C. Chinatown Program, also known as the Chinatown Team, or Chinatown Committee other miscellaneous materials. This material dates from 1988-92.
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: 618-620 H St -- alteration proposal, 1980 October 31 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Meeting notice, agenda, minutes, 1982 December 07 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Meeting notice, minutes, "Economic Analysis of Chinatown", comments on Analysis, 1982 December 21 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Memo "Priorities in the Development of DC's Chinatown", 1982 December 21 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Purpose Statement, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Meeting notice, agenda, minutes, 1982 January 18 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Meeting notice, 1983 February 27 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Minutes, 1983 July 19 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Meeting notice, agenda, membership and officer qualifications, 1983 July 25 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Request for meeting venue, meeting notice, minutes, 1983 October 31 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Meeting notice, 1983 November 28 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Meeting notice, 1984 January 11 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Committee membership, 1984 May (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Meeting notice, minutes, 1984 May 02 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Meeting notice, minutes, 1984 May 17 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Agenda, 1984 June 22 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Request for meeting venue, meeting notice, minutes, presentation of "The Chinatown Program-Part of a Living Downtown", 1984 July 25 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Meeting notice, 1984 September 12 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Minutes, 1984 October 09 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Minutes, 1984 November 14 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Correspondence -- compliments from the Deputy mayor to the Committee, 1984 February 05 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Testimony for the District of Columbia Zoning Commission "The Techworld Project", 1984 December 13 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Various Drafts of the Washington Chinatown Steering Committee's By-Laws, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: The Final By-Laws of the Washington Steering Committee, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Minutes, 1985 January 09 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Minutes, 1985 February 04 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Correspondence -- Invitation to participate on the Public Advisory Committee, 1985 August 07 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: 11/06/1985 -- request for meeting venue, undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Committee membership, 1986 February (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Correspondence -- from Chief Downtown Section office of planning, 1986 February 03 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Minutes, 1986 April 07 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Correspondence (draft) express concern over non-implementation of Columbia Comprehensive plan Act of 1984, 1986 April 14 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Meeting notice, minutes, 1986 May 05 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Correspondence -- Kai Tong Design Associates, Inc Activity update, 1986 May 05 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Minutes, 1986 June 02 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Request for meeting venue, 1986 February 17 (Box 5, Folder 00029A)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Minutes, 1987 December 01 (Box 5, Folder 00029B)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Minutes, The Chinatown Program in 1987 working draft, 1987 February 02 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Memorandum -- attendance policy, 1987 February 24 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Minutes, March February, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Minutes, 1987 April 06 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Agenda, minutes,August March, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Agenda, 1987 October 05 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Minutes, 1987 November 02 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Minutes, 1987 November 16 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Minutes, 1987 December 07 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Minutes, resolution on design concept of the Far East Trade Center, 1988 January 11 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Agenda, minutes, 1988 February 01 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Minutes, attendance list, correspondence -- response to the presentation of the Joint Project Preserving Small Buildings Downtown, 1988 March 07 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Comments on the Joint Project on Preserving Small Buildings in Downtown, 1988 April 14 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Correspondence "Implementing the District Elements of the Comprehensive Plan for the National Capital", 1988 June 10 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Testimony Transcript of Mr. Lee at the Council hearing on the Comprehensive, 1988 June 21 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Correspondence -- project presentation, 1988 July 06 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Agenda, minutes, attendance list, 1988 July 11 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Committee By-Laws, 1988 July 25 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Petition -- re-schedule election of Co-chairman, 1988 August 01 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Agenda, minutes, 1988 August 01 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Meeting notice, agenda, minutes, 1988 September 12 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Meeting notice, agenda, correspondence, 501 G St renovation project, 1988 October 03 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Correspondence -- endorsement of renovation projects, 1988 October 12 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Meeting notice, agenda, design sketch, 1988 November 14 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Meeting notice, agenda, fact sheet on development in Square 428, 1988 December 05 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Annual attendance List, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Meeting notice, agenda, minutes, attendance list, endorsement of DRI project, 1989 January 05 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Sign approvals, 1989 February 13 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Agenda, meeting notice, minutes, sign applications, 1989 March 13 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Agenda, minutes, attendance list, 1989 April 03 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Agenda, minutes, 1989 June 05 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Correspondence -- announces signature of mayor's order 89-132, 1989 July 03 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Meeting notice, agenda, minutes, 1989 July 01 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Minutes, agenda, 1989 August 07 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Meeting notice, agenda, presentation of Marlo Furniture design review, 1989 September 01 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Agenda, 1989 September 26 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Meeting notice, agenda, minutes, attendance list, 1989 October 02 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Agenda, rejection of Downtown Development District draft proposal, 1989 November 06 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Correspondence -- resolution to oppose all down zoning in Chinatown, 1989 December 05 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Agenda, minutes, 1989 December 09 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Chinatown Steering Committee: Minutes, 1990 January 08 (Box 5, Folder 70)